<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Happiness on Jakshi&#39;s casual blog</title>
    <link>http://life.jakshi.com/tags/happiness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Happiness on Jakshi&#39;s casual blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2012-2016 Kostiantyn Lysenko.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 22:17:54 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://life.jakshi.com/tags/happiness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Happiness</title>
      <link>http://life.jakshi.com/post/happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 22:17:54 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://life.jakshi.com/post/happiness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Happiness is controversial fellow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally incline to opinion from this author/article:
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bakadesuyo.com/2015/03/make-you-happy/&#34;&gt;The 5 Daily Rituals That Will Make You Happy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In short:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take Recess.&lt;/strong&gt; Productivity based on balance between work and rest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Switch Autopilot On.&lt;/strong&gt; Stop thinking too much over insignificant things. Example: You see a &lt;em&gt;nice comb&lt;/em&gt;, you start thinking - should I buy it or not? Is it a good idea? May be this one is overpriced, and you can find one 30 baht cheaper? Does this a really important matter? if not - just do whatever you want now, allow autopilot to lead you and relax.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unshackle Yourself.&lt;/strong&gt; Don&amp;rsquo;t try to do everything, do what&amp;rsquo;s important for you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Value your relationships.&lt;/strong&gt; Human are social animals, we are sad when we are alone (usually).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tolerate Some Discomfort.&lt;/strong&gt; Great things come through some discomfort. Cite: &amp;ldquo;heavy TV viewers, and in particular those with significant opportunity cost of time, report lower life satisfaction. Long TV hours are also linked to higher material aspirations and anxiety.&amp;rdquo;. Don&amp;rsquo;t sit and watch TV/browse internet, go out for a walk, swim in the pool (with big inflatable crocodile), learn something new. Going out of super comfort zone worth it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>